<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<custom-objects xmlns="http://www.demandware.com/xml/impex/customobject/2006-10-31">
    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="craignagovan">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Coal Valley, IL</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Craig Nagovan</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1985</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Bernie Schultz">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">Most shallow fish are caught by a clean presentation rather then by a lure's color or action. Make sure your casts are made with stealth, as well as accuracy.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Sight-fishing in shallow water.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">Watching my 10 year old son catch his first permit on the flats in the Florida Keys. It was a true battle - one where the fish was winning until the very end. My wife also witnessed the event and we talk about it to this day.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Lake Ontario (northern lake) and Lake Okeechobee (southern lake).</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Surfing and collecting antique tackle.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Gainesville, Florida</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/bernie-schultz.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;X-Rap 10&lt;/span&gt;- This lure can work virtually anytime of the year, including the dead of winter where bass suspend along steep, vertical banks. Or it can be effective over submerged grassbeds in relatively shallow water. The X-Rap's erratic, slashing action is second to none and makes it my preferred lure whenever fish (any gamefish - fresh or salt) are scattered or inactive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Original Floating Minnow&lt;/span&gt;- This is my all-time favorite for catching fish along bare banks or around sparse cover. In clearer water, it's like a magnet for cruising fish. When the bite gets really tough, I throw this lure on a spinning outfit with 8 to 10 pound line, making long casts so as not to spook the fish. It's bailed me out of some really tough tournaments and nearly won a Bass event on Lake Okeechobee for me! To me, the Original Floating Minnow represents the purest form of artificial minnow - it's a legendary design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT-6&lt;/span&gt;- This is my favorite medium-running crankbait. In 2004, I tied it on for the Bass opener in Florida and never took it off the entire season. It produced great catches of bass for me throughout the season, in all kinds of conditions, on a wide variety of lakes and rivers. It's my absolute go-to crankbait. The colors I prefer include: red crawfish (cooler months) and blue-chartreuse (warmer months). I crank it along sloping 45-degree banks, riprap, through shallow ditches, around docks, laydowns, cypress trees, and especially where rock is mixed with brush. A steady pace retrieve is all that's needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Skitter Walk&lt;/span&gt;- Anytime fish school, I want a Skitter Walk rigged and ready. It casts like a rocket and its deep resonating "knocker" really calls fish from a distance. I've seen both smallmouth and largemouth swim up from 20 feet of water to crush this lure. Besides bass, I use it on the flats in saltwater for tarpon, snook, trout, and reds. Its success is well documented throughout the coastal waters of my home state (Florida). It walks better than any lure in its class. On reservoirs and water clarity and comfortable temperatures, bass usually respond aggressively to the walking action of this lure. If I'm fishing it over submerged cover, I always try stalling the bait directly over key objects, then restarting the walking action this can be a killer method for pulling big fish out of stumps, brushpiles, or from holes in submerged grass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt;- This lure works when nothing else will. When fishing is tough, I tie it on to a medium-action cranking rod and start running the bank. If there's a fish around, chances are good it will bite a Shad Rap. It's been my experience that this lure excels when small shad are the primary forage in any given body of water. I've made it work around docks, along rocky 45 degree banks, and even over submerged weedbeds. It's a truly versatile lure, so long as there's some type of similar forage it can mimic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have to include the &lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;SubWalk&lt;/span&gt;- This is the most exciting new lure design since the X-Rap. I've had success fishing it both in fresh and saltwater. If you know how to walk-the-dog with a topwater lure, you can easily fish this subsurface lure. It works well for saltwater species in skinny water situations like those found on coastal flats and it can also draw bass and stripers from the depths of inland reservoirs. It's like the ultimate go-between for jerkbaits and topwaters. It catches fish when they are reluctant to travel all the way to the surface and the strikes are deliberate and vicious. My best success has been over submerged weedbeds in warmer conditions. That's when this lure seems to shine.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Bernie Schultz</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">I guess it would have to be the Shad Rap. Whether I'm fishing a natural lake or an impoundment, the Shad Rap seems to catch fish when other lures fail.  So long as there is reasonable water clarity, this tight-wiggling lure can entice fish that would otherwise pass up the offering. It's also a good wintertime lure, when bass are slow to react to most lures. There's something about its swimming action that makes it one of the most reliable crankbaits made.  There's not a pro on tour that would be caught without one!</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">DT Fat: I've waited on this lure for years - and believe me, it was well worth the wait! The DT Fat is a shallow-water angler's dream. With its wide profile and exaggerated wobble, the DT Fat can plow through the thickest cover imaginable, including stumps, flooded brush, and laydown trees. The DT Fat deflects off hard cover almost as well as a spinnerbait. I throw it on heavy line (17 - 20 pound test) into places where fish never see a crankbait. When water becomes stained or off-color, bass will position themselves in shallower cover, particularly wooden cover.  That's when this lure will shine.  Throw it just like you would a spinnerbait and bang it against as many branches or twigs possible. It will blow your mind what you can get a way with using the DT Fat.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/bernie-schultz-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.bernieschultzfishing.com/</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1985</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Brad Leifermann">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">When I was fishing with Minnesota Twins baseball greats, Johan Santana and Carlos Santana, in the Kent Hrbek Bass Classic, we hand lined a 4lb largemouth caught on a Rapala DT 10.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Deep water crank bait fishing.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">Seeing family at fishing tournaments.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Mississippi River because of its beauty.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Upland bird hunting and exercising.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Andover, Minnesota</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/brad-leifermann.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Skitter Prop&lt;/span&gt; - For topwater action for both large and smallmouth bass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - #5 Shad Rap for getting bites when fishing is tough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;X-Rap&lt;/span&gt; - X-Rap 10, hot pink for jerk bait smallies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT&lt;/span&gt; - DT 3 for off colored shallow crankin'. DT 16 for deep water banging for pigs.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Brad Leifermann</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Shad Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">DT Fat</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/brad-leifermann-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1985</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Chris Gilman">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">In the 2007 FLW Walleye Tour, I placed in the top 13 in all four tournaments. Rapala products played a key role in all of the tournaments.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Trolling or casting crankbaits.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">&lt;p&gt;This question is impossible to answer. A lot of the best days of my life have been spent fishing. Even though I have won a lot of tournaments and titles, some of my favorite fishing memories center around the fishing opener in Northern Wisconsin. Every year since I was 3, we would camp on an island on a small lake in Northern Wisconsin. I would look forward to that weekend for months ahead of time. It was simpler back then. All we had was a canoe, four or five fishing poles, a tent, hatchet, and some tackle. I trapped my own minnows and would stay up all night on the opener hoping to get a walleye. The time spent with family and friends on the Wisconsin opener are some of my greatest fishing memories. Those days taught me a lot of lessons and helped me become who I am today.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Lake Winnebago System</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Chisago City, Minnesota</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/chris-gilman.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;It depends on the lake or river, but I had to rank my arsenal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - All sizes and colors. Still the best for casting or trolling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Husky Jerk&lt;/span&gt; - Shallow and deep. I have won a lot of money on these.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Original Floater&lt;/span&gt; - There is nothing better for three way rigs in the rivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Storm Hot 'n Tot&lt;/span&gt; - When big fish will bite a lure that is going fast, nothing is better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;VMC Fast Grip Hooks&lt;/span&gt; - Why miss a fish?&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Chris Gilman</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Shad Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Shad Rap #5</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/chris-gilman-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1996</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Dave Lefebre">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">The first bass I ever caught was on a 4\" floating silver Rapala. I used to collect Rapala lures from 1980-1990 until my collection was stolen! I had every size and every color original and countdown made... even Huskys. I still have old Husky Jerks with huge teeth marks on them.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Flipping, pitching, skipping jigs and shallow cranking.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">Taking my son, Mitchell out in the boat for the first time and watching him light up when he hooked a big crappie. He's 5 years old now and is ate up with fishing like I was... and still am!</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Presque Isle Bay, Lake Erie</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Writing songs, playing drums, ice fishing and watching Steelers games.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Union City, Pennsylvania</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/dave-lefebre.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;CountDown&lt;/span&gt; - The CD 9 can be fished super slow for pre-spawn sluggish fish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Skitter Walk&lt;/span&gt; - Topwater pattern when water has chop to it - super loud rattle, throws water!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - I add a weight to the tiny SR 5 (Silver, Shad, Gold) around schooling fish that are not biting. They can't resist it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT 10&lt;/span&gt; - Best 10' crankbait on the market, when fishing 6' - 10' structure!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Jigging Rap&lt;/span&gt; - When the lake is frozen.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Dave Lefebre</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">DT 6 - Great for covering a lot of water in a hurry. Parrot and Silver are probably my two favorite color patterns!</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Skitter Walk (Shad Translucent) - I caught several big fish on it this season in tournaments.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/dave-lefebre-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.davelefebre.com</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">2003</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Mark Fisher">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">The first time I fished a Rapala (which was a #09 Gold Floater) was with my father at the age of 9 while on vacation. I caught a blue gill on the front treble and a walleye on the tail hook at the same time... honest.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Deep Cranking structure with DT 10's, 16'S and 20's.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">The next time I take someone fishing... they're all favorites.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Rainy Lake, Ontario</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Old pick-up trucks and bonfires with a lot of smoke.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Nowthen, Minnesota</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/mark-fisher.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;Depending on the species of choice, best advice would be to take along a mix of lures best suited for that fish. I would also carry along a few that are simply "go-to" multi-species lures such as the Floaters and Shad Raps in several sizes. If the fishing gets tough or the weather turns cold... remember to down size the lure and go smaller.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Mark Fisher</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">For success catching walleyes while drifting and casting, it would be a #11 Minnow Rap. For big Pike a #15 SubWalk. For smallies a #10 X-Rap and Largemouth a DT 10.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">With so many favorites to chose from I'd have to pick the Clackin' Rap. I'm catching a lot of fish on them and finding new applications for them. It's simply a fun lure to fish and have fun with.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/mark-fisher-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Mark Martin">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Trolling or casting Rapala crankbaits</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">Fishing with my dad and grandpa all night long for trophy walleyes has made me who I am today.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Saginaw Bay</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Hunting whitetail deer.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Twin Lake, Michigan</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/mark-martin.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Original Floater&lt;/span&gt; - Used for slow presentations with or without curren and with or without weight added to line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - Used for targeting different structures at different depths whether casting or trolling dirty or clear waters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Husky Jerk&lt;/span&gt; - Used for targeting fish all year long at all depths, all speeds, all water conditions - lake, river, reservoir, and all water colors from clean to dirty.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Mark Martin</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">The Orginal Floater is my "go to" lure.  It can be made to catch fish at any depth and any body of water, day and night.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">The tail dancer was my big fish catcher (10.59lbs) at the Little Boy Tournament PWI.  Plus many more fish caught throughtout the year.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/mark-martin-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1985</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Mike Gofron">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">You can remove a hook or two to let your lure run through the cover true to its capability, instead of fouling up with weeds and getting snagged.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Casting cranks and jigging.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">Winning the PWT Championship.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Missouri River System</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Duck hunting, fourwheeling, and watching my kids play sports.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Antioch, Illinois</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/mike-gofron.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - Great for shallow water trolling. The Shad Rap always runs true at high speeds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Orginal Floater&lt;/span&gt; - There is nothing better in the spring over the tops of shallow weed growth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Deep Husky Jerk&lt;/span&gt; - Produces in the Great Lakes by fishing 5' - 18' on boards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Tail Dancer&lt;/span&gt; - I use this one in the Great Lakes as well. It has a wider wobble and makes more noise in the water column to attract attention.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Mike Gofron</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Shad Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Shad Rap Perch &amp; Gold for casting and trolling.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/mike-gofron-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.mikegofron.com</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1989</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Ron Hueston">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">My first cast ever with my Dad. I was five years old, threw out a Rapala Original Floater, black and gold, and a largemouth bass followed it all the way back to the bank. Since then, I have been hooked on fishing.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Naples, Florida</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/ron-hueston.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">Skitter Walk, Twitchin' Rap, X-Rap, SubWalk, Shad Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Ron Hueston</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Twitchin' Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Twitchin' Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/ron-hueston-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1999</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Terry Bolton">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Deep water structure fishing</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">In March of 1994, I caught a 7 bass limit that weighed 37lbs. This catch included 4 bass over 7lbs and some of them were caught on a Shad Rap.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Kentucky Lake</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Duck hunting and tennis</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Jonesboro, Arkansas</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/terry-bolton.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - #1 bait for early Spring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT 16&lt;/span&gt; - Best deep structure crankbait on the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT 6&lt;/span&gt; - Great bait for cranking grass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;DT Fat&lt;/span&gt; - Great for cranking shallow wood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;X-Rap SureSet&lt;/span&gt; - Great for action and colors.&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Terry Bolton</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Shad Rap</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">DT Fat</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/terry-bolton-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1994</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Tom Neustrom">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="didYouKnow">While guiding two anglers one October, I fell in the lake while netting my customers walleye. The other angler sets the hook on another fish and as he brought it to the boat he yells, "While you're in there, could you net mine too?"</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Husky Jerks over rocks and swimming large soft plastics.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">I netted my Dad's first musky and was with my Dad when he finally caught "The Leroy Brown Bass" that he fished for all his life. He finally caught it on a #9 Silver Floating Rapala (and I have the bait) which is hanging in my garage. The bass was 6lbs 14oz.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Dogtooth, Pokegama, Deer Lake, and Florida Keys.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Fishing, talking about fishing, scripting radio commercials, fishing, and fishing with my wife Renee.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Grand Rapids, Minnesota</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/tom-neustrom.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - #5 Shad Rap for trolling large expanses of shallow water (6-8 feet).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Minnow Rap&lt;/span&gt; - #11 Minnow Rap... I can cast or troll it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Husky Jerk&lt;/span&gt; - Husky Jerks in different sizes, irratic action makes it a fish catching machine in most shallow conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Original Floater&lt;/span&gt; - Original Floater #9 and #13... I like to slow troll them at night over the tops of cabbage weed and rocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Tail Dancer #7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Tom Neustrom</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Husky Jerk - When species are shallow, it's tough to beat.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Minnow Rap #11 and Tail Dancer (Big Pike on Pokegama).</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/tom-neustrom-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.mnfishingconnections.com</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1980</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Johnnie Candle">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoriteTechnique">Trolling crankbaits</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">I can still remember my fist 10lb. walleye. It came on a day fishing with my father and grandfather. That made it even better. Lake Erie's central basin 300' back, 10lb wire line, Deep Thunderstick, lime green specks.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Tobin Lake, Saskatchewan</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="hobbies">Other than fishing, I love to hunt whitetail deer.</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Devils Lake, North Dakota</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/johnnie-candle.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap RS&lt;/span&gt; - #4 and #5 Shad Rap RS for casting to shallow early season walleye.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Deep Husky Jerk&lt;/span&gt; - #10 and #12 Deep Husky Jerks for trolling cold water suspended eyes in the Great Lakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Deep Tail Dancer&lt;/span&gt; - Deep Tail Dancers get to the big ones down deep in lakes in Summer and Fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-weight: bold;"&gt;Shad Rap&lt;/span&gt; - #5 and #7 Shad Raps to "match the hatch" during mid-summer when bait size is critical. #9 Shad Raps for the times you need the BIG bite!&lt;/p&gt;</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Johnnie Candle</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">#7 Shad Rap in Fire Tiger - I can always get a walleye to eat one!</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">Yellow Perch Shad Raps - This color will rock em' everywhere!</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/johnnie-candle-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.johnniecandle.com</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1994</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

    <custom-object type-id="ProStaff" object-id="Mike Iaconelli">
        <object-attribute attribute-id="bluefoxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritefishingmemory">&lt;p&gt;By the time I was twelve, I had been fishing trout in the Poconos with my family for over ten years. I&amp;rsquo;d caught a few bass up to that point, but they were little. A fingerling (a couple of inches long) to maybe half a foot, tops. And I had never caught one on purpose. The only time I even used artificial baits was trolling around, usually with basic inline spinners. So heading up to the lake that June, I was just looking forward to another week of catching trout and having fun. I had no idea my life was about to change.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The first morning of that summer&amp;rsquo;s trip to the Poconos, I hit the dock to cast a few before Pop and Uncle Don came out. It was just gonna be another day of trout fishing, but today, Pop&amp;rsquo;s box kept calling my name. Maybe it was the excitement of being back at the lake, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist going in and grabbing something to throw off the dock. I pulled out a 9S Floating Rapala - black on the back, silver sides, two treble hooks: one on the belly, one on the tail. At the time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know what it was. I just reached into the Coleman and pulled it out.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The scene is still vivid in my mind. I&amp;rsquo;m out on the end of the T-dock, there&amp;rsquo;s a little fog on the lake, and the water is slick and calm. My rod was still rigged to catch panfish and trout, which meant line out of the reel attached to a swivel, a snelled hook, and a Water Gremlin split shot.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;So I pinched the ears of the Gremlin, popped it off, and attached the Rapala, with absolutely no idea how to fish it or what it was going to do in the water. All I knew how to do was cast, which by now I did pretty well. I threw out the Rapala in a big, beautiful arc and it hit the water, ripples moving away as it hit the water. It just floated there. That&amp;rsquo;s what it was supposed to do, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For the first few seconds, I just stared at this strange, floating bait. Then I gave the reel four or five cranks, watching the Rapala&amp;rsquo;s swimming action. I was astonished. I&amp;rsquo;d never seen a lure behave like that. And as I thought, &amp;ldquo;Okay, it&amp;rsquo;s a bait you cast, swim and reel in,&amp;rdquo; the bait floated back to the surface, where I let it sit for another couple seconds. &lt;em&gt;Whoosh!&lt;/em&gt; This bass - not a giant, but at almost three pounds it was the biggest fish I&amp;rsquo;d ever seen- blew out of the water, mouth wide open, swallowing the Rapala. The visual was the most intense thing I&amp;rsquo;d ever seen. In trout fishing, you drag live bait along the bottom of the water, watching your rod tip or bobber. I had never seen a fish explode out of the water after a lure. I don&amp;rsquo;t even think I set the hook! If the bass hadn&amp;rsquo;t totally engulfed that lure, I probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have brought it in.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I could barely breathe, as I used every ounce of energy to land that fish. It gave me a fight like I&amp;rsquo;d never experienced, bulldogging me and splashing all the way back to the dock. I was flipping out, thinking, &amp;ldquo;If that line breaks, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have to fess up to taking the lure, and replace it... &lt;em&gt;And nobody&amp;rsquo;s gonna believe I caught it to begin with!&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; It was a situation where I had to beat that fish, the first of many over the course of my career.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Once I had it on the dock, I started screaming bloody murder, running back to cabin 3, where we were staying that year. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even know how to hold a bass back then, so I just ran with the fish hanging off the end of my line. &amp;ldquo;Aaaaaaagggghhh!&amp;rdquo; My family must have thought I was being stabbed to death by some lakeside killer. I busted through the door, the bass dangling off my rod tip like a hanging grenade, and everybody freaked. Pop thought it was the biggest fish in the world. And not being a catch-and-release guy, the first thing out of his mouth was &amp;ldquo;Get my stringer! Put him on the stringer!&amp;rdquo; My new buddy was getting some Crisco and bread</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="favoritelake">Palatine</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="homeTown">Pittsgrove, New Jersey</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="largeImage">images/proStaff/large/mike-iaconelli.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="luhrjensenbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="musthaveluresandwhy">Original Floater, Shad Rap, CountDown, DT Dives-To</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="newicon">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="proanglername">Mike Iaconelli</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="rapalabrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="stormbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="sufixbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="terminatorbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="theonegotorapalalure">Original Floater</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="thisyearsfavoriterapalalure">DT Thug</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="tileImage">images/proStaff/tile/mike-iaconelli-thumb.jpg</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="triggerxbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="vmcbrand">true</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="website">http://www.mikeiaconelli.com/</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="williamsonbrand">false</object-attribute>
        <object-attribute attribute-id="yearTurnedPro">1998</object-attribute>
    </custom-object>

</custom-objects>
